<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HCI | Rongtao Zhang</title>
    <link>https://isanshi.github.io/tag/hci/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://isanshi.github.io/tag/hci/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>HCI</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://isanshi.github.io/media/icon_hu0abe02584a566683a89c96345314bcf2_17128_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>HCI</title>
      <link>https://isanshi.github.io/tag/hci/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personalizing Haptic Signals using Preference-Based Reward Learning</title>
      <link>https://isanshi.github.io/project/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isanshi.github.io/project/project-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mediated touch can convey both discriminative and affective information, with its impact largely dependent on the touch receiver’s interpretation of the stimuli. Since this interpretation varies across individuals, incorporating personal differences into the touch signal generation process can enhance the intelligence of haptic systems and improve the efficiency of mediated touch communication. This study explores the use of data-efficient preference-based reward learning (PbRL)
to capture individual tactile perceptual differences and preferences. Our user study (N=12) addresses the limitations of one-size-fits-all designs in haptic experiences. Our proposed method demonstrates the potential to capture individual preferences and effectively optimize haptic signals for specific goals, such as comfort versus attention-grabbing. These findings underscore the importance of personalization in haptic design and highlight the potential of PbRL to create user-centered adaptive tactile experiences for future research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This work is being conducted under the guidance of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cs.usc.edu/directory/faculty/profile/?lname=Culbertson&amp;fname=Heather&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Heather Culbertson&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ebiyik.github.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Erdem Bıyık&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and led by &lt;a href=&#34;https://xinzhu.us&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xin Zhu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
